Hi, I'm JIGNESH DEVJI.

Professional summary

Undergraduate of Computer science with a keen interest in IT Operations, Networking and Software Engineering. A strong team collaborator and keen to learn and work with new technology. Experience in using programming languages such as Python, Java, JavaScript HTML5 and Bash. Confident with Nodejs, MySQL and MongoDB. Well Organised with strong communication skills, time management skills and technical abilities.

Experience

O

O CATERER Jun 2017 - Aug 2019

RUBYS CATERING, Alperton, United Kingdom

- Regularly Attended events to cater food for over 500 guests.
- Responsible for taking delivery of food at the venue and organising dishes into presentable trays ready to serve the guests.
- Co-ordinated a team of people in organising the dining room in accordance with the customers desired specifications. This ensured there would be no disappointments when the guests arrive.
- Organised cutlery in patterns with great attention to detail in accordance with the customers' requirements.
- Ensured the customers were happy with our service and acted swiftly on feedback given. This kept the reputation of the company thriving.
- Ensured the team cleared the venue before the clients lease of the building was over. This made sure we did not clash with other events that were going to take place later on.

IT Operations/Infrastructure Engineer May 2017 - Nov 2018 HENDON SECONDARY SCHOOL, Hendon, United Kingdom

- Provided 1st and 2nd line support to students and members of staff and successfully resolved their technical issues and ensured they were left satisfied.
- Automated the Operating System installation process to allow the seamless integration of new computer systems into the network, exceeding my managers expectations.
- Managed Server Roles and Services with the supervision of the System Administrator.
- Created Bash Scripts to automate the process of configuring domain group policies and installing software on new client machines and slashed the time it takes to configure new computer systems by 80%.
- Gained Experience in working with Active Directory (AD) and providing user access control which kept the schools various pool of resources safe from unauthorised access.
- Maintained Hardware and Software across the school's fleet of Laptops and Desktop Computers which ensured the systems performed efficiently and effectively.
- Gained Working Knowledge of Windows Server 2012 R2 editions and later which has set me up to work in other environments with similar IT infrastructure.

Contact

jigneshdevji@hotmail.com

• Greater London, United Kingdom

My LinkedIn Profile:

https://www.linkedin.co m/in/jignesh-devji-47ba60205

Skills

Python,
Node.js,
MongoDB,
CSS 3,
MySQL,
HTML 5,
Java,
JavaScript,
Bash,
Linux,
Windows Server,
Microsoft Office,
Active Directory,
Attention to Detail,

Team Player,
Communication,
Responsible,
Problem Solver

INTERN TEACHING ASSISTANT May 2017 - Jul 2017

- Worked in a team to teach coding to Year 8 students.
- Took Responsibility to read and learn about Visual Basic programming
- Took and abstract approach to explain concepts so that 12year-olds would understand. This ensured the students remained interested and would keep in attendance of the weekly lessons.
- Created fun and engaging PowerPoint presentations to explain key programming concepts. This allowed students to remain focussed and pay attention to the content I taught.
- Setup practical labs with easy-to-follow tutorials which allowed students to put theory into practise. Learning to code by being practical made sure the students mastered the concepts and were ready to advance to the next stage.
- Communicated alterations and cancelations of weekly lessons to all students via email so that they never miss a lesson and always remain up to date with their learning.

Education

O BACHELOR OF SCIENCE - COMPUTER SCIENCE

Aug 2021

Goldsmiths University of London, United Kingdom

Achieved: 1st Class Honours